Finding Aid to the Nancy Stoller Papers, 1981-1995 MSS 2000-6
University of California, San Francisco Archives & Special Collections
- AIDS Subject Files, 1981-1995; Series 1; 144 Folders: Carton 1 Folders 1/1-1/71, Carton 2 Folders 2/1-2/73
  - Miscellaneous AIDS (Carton 2, Folder 72-73)
    - Separated or Unassigned AIDS Materials, 1987-1994 (Carton 2, Folder 72)
    - Organizational Directories and Address Lists, 1988-1995 (Carton 2, Folder 73)
- Organizations, 1984-1995; Series 2; 263 Folders: Cartons 3-7 Folders 3/1-7/14
  This series contains materials similar to those found in the subject files, but Stoller classified them by organization rather than subject. There are fewer newspaper clippings and more minutes and other administrative documents in this Series. Quantity and quality of materials in this series range from a single fundraising letter from The Names Project to an extensive collection of San Francisco AIDS Foundation documents.
  This series is further subdivided into 6 subseries, The first two subseries consist of an aggregate of organizations on which Stoller has amassed a small or medium amount of material, the next 3 subseries each represent one of the organizations that Stoller actively worked with/observed during her hiatus from UCSCIRCA The final subseries contains materials from several Women's Organizations. The subseries are: A. Geographical (Small); B. Alphabetical (Medium); Subseries C: SFAF; Subseries D: CAL-PEP (California Prostitutes Education Project); Subseries E: ACT-UP New York City; Subseries F: Women's Organizations.
  This is a modification of Stoller's order. She had the organizations with just one or two folders of information separated from the those with a large or middle-sized amount of folders. The large and mid-sized groupings were in no distinguishable order. The organizations with the largest number of folders (which correspond to the groups in which Stoller was most active) have been given individual sub-series for ease in description. Stoller appeared to have kept the various women's related organizations together, so this was retained as the final subseries.
  - Geographical (Small), 1984-1993; Subseries 2.1; 36 Folders: Carton 3 Folders 3/1-3/36
    This subseries contains from one to two folders on each of a number of AIDS organizations or AIDS related projects of non-AIDS specific organizations. There is also one folder of material from the American Family Association, a right wing propaganda organization denouncing gays and AIDS. The materials in this subseries vary greatly, The Gay Men's Health Crisis folder contains only a single letter from Stoller, while the National Gay Task Force, the California and Santa Cruz AIDS Projects, and a few other organizations take up two folders each. The subseries is arranged alphabetically by regional subdivisions: Northern California/Bay Area Organizations, Southern California, and New York and National Groups.
    Of special note are the following: The AAPCHO (Association of Asian/Pacific Community Health Organization) folder includes information on the film "Behind the Masks: AIDS... It Affects All of Us." The AWARE Study folder contains information on a UCSF Study for which Stoller was a consultant and Constance Wofsy was principal investigator. SAMHA (Substance Abuse and Mental Health in AIDS) was another cooperative project between UCSF, UCB and Hunter's Point organizations. The Santa Cruz AIDS Project material includes AIDS Prevention in Public Sex Environments (1990). The CARE AIDS Prevention for Substance Abuse Treatment Programs folder contains AIDS Prevention for Substance Abuse Treatment Programs, published by the State of New York.
    - Northern California/Bay Area Organizations (Carton 3, Folder 1-26)
      - AAPCHO (Association of Asian/Pacific Community Health Organization), 1990 (Carton 3, Folder 1)
      - AIDS Action Pledge, San Francisco, 1988; undated (Carton 3, Folder 2)
      - AIDS Conscious, Saratoga, CA, 1986 (Carton 3, Folder 3)
      - AIDS Health Project, San Francisco, 1985; 1990-1991 (Carton 3, Folder 4)
      - Alameda County Health Care Services, 1985 (Carton 3, Folder 5)
      - AWARE Study, 1985-1986 (Carton 3, Folder 6)
      - BACW (Bay Area Career Women )- AIDS and the Women's Community, 1986 (Carton 3, Folder 7)
      - California AIDS Project (Carton 3, Folder 8-9)
        - SFAF Contract, 1985 (Carton 3, Folder 8)
        - California AIDS Project - Educational Services, 1984-1985 (Carton 3, Folder 9)
      - California Department of Health Services, Sacramento (Carton 3, Folder 10-11)
        - Draft AIDS Documents, 1987 (Carton 3, Folder 10)
        - Underserved Minority Populations, 1986 (Carton 3, Folder 11)
      - California Mobilization Against AIDS (San Francisco), 1985 (Carton 3, Folder 12)
      - FACET (Family Addiction Center for Education & Treatment), 1985 (Carton 3, Folder 13)
      - The Names Project San Francisco, undated (Carton 3, Folder 14)
      - Oakland Feminist Health Center, undated (Carton 3, Folder 15)
      - Parents Action for Children's Cancer Treatment, circa 1985 (Carton 3, Folder 16)
      - Planned Parenthood, 1985 (Carton 3, Folder 17)
      - SAMHA (Substance Abuse and Mental Health in AIDS), 1987 (Carton 3, Folder 18)
      - San Francisco Department of Social Service, undated (Carton 3, Folder 19)
      - Santa Cruz AIDS Project (Carton 3, Folder 20-21)
        - AIDS Service Directory and other materials, 1985-1986 (Carton 3, Folder 20)
        - AIDS Prevention in Public Sex Environments (1990) - Outreach and Training (Carton 3, Folder 21)
      - Shanti Project, 1985; 1993 (Carton 3, Folder 22)
      - Sperm Bank of Northern California, undated (Carton 3, Folder 23)
      - Stop AIDS Project, San Francisco, 1985 (Carton 3, Folder 24)
      - Vanguard Foundation, 1985 (Carton 3, Folder 25)
      - Women's Blood Drive/Harvey Milk Democratic Club, 1985 (Carton 3, Folder 26)
    - Southern California (Carton 3, Folder 27-28)
      - AIDS Project Los Angeles - Living with AIDS: A Self-Care Manual, circa 1985 (Carton 3, Folder 27)
      - Los Angeles County Drug Abuse Program, 1988 (Carton 3, Folder 28)
    - New York and National Groups (Carton 3, Folder 29-36)
      - American Family Association, 1991-1992 (Carton 3, Folder 29)
      - AIDS Action Council, 1987; undated (Carton 3, Folder 30)
      - CARE AIDS Prevention for Substance Abuse Treatment Programs, New York, 1987 (Carton 3, Folder 31)
      - Gay Men's Health Crisis [New York], 1985 (Carton 3, Folder 32)
      - National Gay Task Force (NGTF) - (Carton 3, Folder 33-34)
        - AIDS Program, 1984 (Carton 3, Folder 33)
        - Bathhouses, 1985 (Carton 3, Folder 34)
      - New York City Task Force on Women & AIDS: Policy Document, undated (Carton 3, Folder 35)
      - Organizational Contacts - National, 1986 (Carton 3, Folder 36)
  - Alphabetical (Medium), 1984-1994; Subseries 2.2; 66 Folders: Carton 3 Folders 3/37-3/68; Carton 4 Folders 4/1-4/34
    This subseries consists of the organizations that Stoller acquired and kept a mid-sized amount of information on. These organizations include: ACHA (American College Health Association - Task Force on the Acquired Immunodeficiency Syndrome (AIDS)), APHA (American Public Health Association), the City of New York and the San Francisco Commissions on Human Rights (HRC), NSBC (National Skills Building Conference), a number of universities (including UCSF, UCSC, UCB, SFSU, and MacQuarie University in Australia), and San Francisco Department of Public Health (SFDPH).
    The ACHA material concerns institutional issues and includes a "Partnering Agreement" with the CDC and a grant application to the American Foundation for AIDS Research.
    APHA "General" file includes Stoller's membership card and other membership materials. The APHA "California Models" file contains a paper by that name along with changes and the Women AIDS - Straight Talk project funding proposal. The New York HRC files include three 1987 Reports by the HRC (at least one of them also in another folder); a series of pamphlets in English and Spanish was moved to the Ephemera Series. The National Skills Building Conference (NSBC) was an annual gathering sponsored by the AIDS National Interfaith Network, National Association of People with AIDS, and the National Minority AIDS Council. The UCSF files contain, among other things, material on the Sept. 13-14, 1985, Administrative and Clinical Issues of Mental Health Conference, and a follow up conference in 1988. There are also drafts and proofs of the article "Women & AIDS" by Shaw and Paleo, in What to do About AIDS, that grew out of the conference. The Social and Behavioral Sciences Department folder includes information on Nancy Stoller Shaw's appointment as "Visiting Lecturer without Salary" at the UCSF Nursing School. The MacQuarie University files includes a large number of papers and reports on studies on gay and bisexual men, co-sponsored by the Australian University and an Australian Government Agency. The San Francisco Department of Public Health (SFDPH) files include a folder of handwritten notes from one or more meetings that Stoller held with Florence (Flo) Stroud on Women & AIDS.
    - ACHA (American College Health Association - Task Force on the Acquired Immunodeficiency Syndrome (AIDS) (Carton 3, Folder 37-45)
      - Communications (Carton 3, Folder 37-40)
        - 1988 (Carton 3, Folder 37)
        - 1987 (Carton 3, Folder 38)
        - 1986-1987 (Carton 3, Folder 39)
        - June 1986-September 1986 (Carton 3, Folder 40)
      - Meeting, May 27-31, 1986 (Carton 3, Folder 41)
      - Coping with AIDS: A Handbook for College and University Physicians and Counselors, undated (Carton 3, Folder 42)
      - Research Articles, 1986-1987 (Carton 3, Folder 43)
      - AIDS on the College Campus: ACHA Special Report, 1986 (Carton 3, Folder 44)
      - Statement on AIDS Antibody Testing, December 1985 (Carton 3, Folder 45)
    - APHA (American Public Health Association) (Carton 3, Folder 46-53)
      - General, 1986-1987 (Carton 3, Folder 46)
      - Paper Proposal, notes and background articles, 1986 (Carton 3, Folder 47)
      - "California Models", 1985-1986 (Carton 3, Folder 48)
      - Las Vegas Meeting, Sept 28-Nov 2, 1986 (Carton 3, Folder 49)
      - Program and Abstracts - APHA 114th Annual Meeting, Las Vegas, 1986 (Carton 3, Folder 50)
      - Washington, D.CIRCA, Nov 17-21, 1985 (Carton 3, Folder 51)
      - "Model Programs for Women's AIDS Education & Services," by Nancy Shaw given at 1985 Annual Meeting (Carton 3, Folder 52)
      - "The Whore Stigma: Female Dishonor and Male Unworthiness" by Gail Pheterson, 1985 (Carton 3, Folder 53)
    - HRC (City of New York Commission on Human Rights) (Carton 3, Folder 54-57)
      - 1989 Handouts, 1986-1989 (Carton 3, Folder 54-55)
      - Notes, 1989 (Carton 3, Folder 56)
      - Memoranda, July 1989 (Carton 3, Folder 57)
    - HRC (San Francisco Human Rights Commission) (Carton 3, Folder 58-61)
      - Sexual Orientation Complaint Report, 1987 (Carton 3, Folder 58)
      - Discrimination Testimony, 1986 (Carton 3, Folder 59)
      - AIDS Related Legislation, 1985-1986 (Carton 3, Folder 60)
      - Lesbian/Gay Advisory Committee, 1985 (Carton 3, Folder 61)
    - NSBC (National Skills Building Conference) (Carton 3, Folder 62-55)
      - Atlanta, Oct. 29 to Nov. 1, 1994, 1993-1994 (Carton 3, Folder 62)
      - Handouts (Papers, Flyers, etcetera), 1994 (Carton 3, Folder 63)
      - Los Angeles, Oct 19-22, 1995 (Carton 3, Folder 64)
      - Contact at 1994 Meeting - Taking Care: The Workshop for Caregivers, circa 1994 (Carton 3, Folder 65)
    - Universities and AIDS, Carton 3 Folder 66 - Carton 4 Folder 26
      - UCSF, Carton 3 Folder 66 - Carton 4 Folder 3
        - AIDS Policy, Administrative and Clinical Issues of Mental Health Conference, Sept. 13-14, 1985, and Mental Health: Beyond the Basics & Care for the Caregiver April 28-30, 1988 (Carton 3, Folder 66)
        - AIDS and Mental Health: Policy, Administration, Treatment papers from Conference, circa 1986 (Carton 3, Folder 67)
        - AIDS and Mental Health Book, 1985-1987 (Carton 3, Folder 68)
        - AIDS Antibody Testing Conference, 1986 (Carton 4, Folder 1)
        - UCSF Institute for Health Policy Studies (IHPS) Antibody Testing Study, 1985 (Carton 4, Folder 2)
        - Social and Behavioral Sciences Department, 1984 (Carton 4, Folder 3)
      - UCSC, 1987-1991 (Carton 4, Folder 4)
      - UCB (Carton 4, Folder 5-7)
        - AIDS Task Force, 1986 (Carton 4, Folder 5)
        - AIDS Policy Seminar, 1986 (Carton 4, Folder 6)
        - AIDS Seminar #2 [Prisons], 1985-1986 (Carton 4, Folder 7)
      - University [of California] -Wide AIDS Research Program: Program Overview and Annual Progress Report, 1990 (Carton 4, Folder 8)
      - SFSU (Carton 4, Folder 9-10)
        - Students, 1985 (Carton 4, Folder 9)
        - AIDS Prevention Project, Nov 11-16, 1985 (Carton 4, Folder 10)
      - MacQuarie University - New South Wales, Australia (Carton 4, Folder 11-26)
        - Social Aspects of the Prevention of AIDS - Study A - Report No. 5: "Practice and Pleasure: Sexuality in a Sample of, 1989 (Carton 4, Folder 11)
        - "Reaching Men who have Sex with Men in Australia: An Overview of AIDS Education: Community Intervention and Community Attachment Strategies" GW Dowsett, 1990 (Carton 4, Folder 12)
        - "Sexuality in the AIDS Crisis: Patterns of Sexual Practice and Pleasure in a Sample of Australian Gay and Bisexual Men." R.W. Connell & Susan Kippax, 1990 (Carton 4, Folder 13)
        - "Gay Men's Knowledge of HIV Transmission and 'Safe' Sex: A Question of Accuracy" Susan Kippax, June Crawford, GW Dowsett, G Bond, V Sinnott, D Baxter, R Berg, RW Connell, & L. Watson, 1990 (Carton 4, Folder 14)
        - "Danger and Context: Unsafe Anal Sexual Practice among Homosexual and Bisexual Men in the AIDS Crisis" RW Connell, GW Dowsett, S Kippax, V Sinnott, P Rodden, R Berg, 1990 (Carton 4, Folder 15)
        - Social Aspects of the Prevention of AIDS - two reports #7 "The Importance of Gay Community in the Prevention of HIV Transmission" (circa1990) and "Discrimination In the Context of AIDS: Disease and Deviance" (1991), 1990-1991 (Carton 4, Folder 16)
        - "Men Who Have Sex With Men: Considerations for a National HIV/AIDS Educational Intervention" GW Dowsett, 1991 (Carton 4, Folder 17)
        - "Bisexually Active Men and Beats: Theoretical and Educational Implications" The Bisexually Active Men's Outreach Project, MD Davis, U Klemmer & GW Dowsett, 1991 (Carton 4, Folder 18)
        - "Social class, gay men and AIDS prevention" RW Connell, GW Dowsett, P Rodden, MD Davis, L Watson, D Baxter, 1991 (Carton 4, Folder 19)
        - "The Contribution of Gay Community to Sexual Behavior Change Among Homosexualy Active Men in Australia" GW Dowsett, Susan Kippax, RW Connell and June Crawford, circa 1991 (Carton 4, Folder 20)
        - "Ways of Using: Functional Injecting Drug Users Project", 1992 (Carton 4, Folder 21)
        - "A Community Based Program of AIDS Prevention Research" RW Connell, 1992 (Carton 4, Folder 22)
        - "Transgression and Intervention: Homosexually Active Men and Beats" GW Dowsett & MD Davis, 1992 (Carton 4, Folder 23)
        - "Structuring HIV Prevention Service Delivery Systems on the Basis of Social Science Theory" Ronald O Valdiserri, Gary R West, Melinda Moore, William Darrow & Alan R Hinman, 1992 (Carton 4, Folder 24)
        - "Gay Men, HIV/AIDS and Social Research: An Antipodean Perspective" Gary Dowsett, Mark Davis & Bob Connell, 1992 (Carton 4, Folder 25)
        - "A Bastard of a Life: Homosexual Desire and Practice among Men in Working-class Milieux" RW Connell, MD Davis, & GW Dowsett, 1992 (Carton 4, Folder 26)
    - San Francisco Department of Public Health (SFDPH) (Carton 4, Folder 27-34)
      - Health Commissioner's Plan for 1987-1988, 1986 (Carton 4, Folder 27)
      - 1987 Monitoring Report, 1987-1988 (Carton 4, Folder 28)
      - Perinatal AIDS Advisory Committee, 1986 (Carton 4, Folder 29)
      - Flo Stroud - handwritten notes on Women & AIDS, 1987 (Carton 4, Folder 30)
      - Muni Ads, 1987 (Carton 4, Folder 31)
      - Lesbian Residential Substance Abuse Task Force, circa 1985 (Carton 4, Folder 32)
      - Women and AIDS Forum, 1985 (Carton 4, Folder 33)
      - Education of Prostitutes, 1985; undated (Carton 4, Folder 34)
  - San Francisco AIDS Foundation (SFAF), 1985-1994; Subseries 2.3; 66 Folders: Carton 4 Folders 4/35-4/71; Carton 5 Folders 5/1-5/29
    This subseries contains materials documenting the work of the San Francisco AIDS Foundation (SFAF). The majority of the materials come from Stoller's time as Women's Program Development Coordinator. Most of the materials are related to her work within the Education Department including work with women, heterosexuals, children, etcetera There is also a large subsection of material on SFAF's work with Intravenous Drug Users. Of special interest is a file concerning responses to Tom Waddell's Article "Don't Take the Test" in ComingUp. The Antibody Testing folder also contains a lot of information on the test/don't test controversy. "Nancy's Timelines" includes her May 12, 1987 resignation letter (she was returning to UCSC) and also the posting for her job from October 1984. The Miscellaneous items folder includes list of current legislation and SFAF's position on each bill. The Annual Report folder contains reports from 1985-1993 (there was no annual report published in 1991), it also includes a fundraising flyer/pamphlet from 1987.
    - Education Department Monthly Reports, 1985 (Carton 4, Folder 35)
    - Miscellaneous Communication, 1985 (Carton 4, Folder 36)
    - People with AIDS Update newsletter, February, 1985 (Carton 4, Folder 37)
    - Support Resources, April, 1985 (Carton 4, Folder 38)
    - Health Department/Florence Stroud Proposals for teenager and minority outreach programs, 1985 (Carton 4, Folder 39)
    - AIDS Discrimination Hearin, 1985-1986 (Carton 4, Folder 40)
    - Women's Support Groups & AHP (AIDS Health Project), March 1985 (Carton 4, Folder 41)
    - Coming Up! - A response to Tom Waddell's Article "Don't Take the Test" (1985) - includes a complete copy of the newspaper with the article (Carton 4, Folder 42)
    - Support Group Listing, May 1985 (Carton 4, Folder 43)
    - San Francisco Health Crisis - Women's focus groups report, June 1985 (Carton 4, Folder 44)
    - Irwin Memorial Blood Bank, July 1985 (Carton 4, Folder 45)
    - Gay Media/Organization Mailing List, August 1985 (Carton 4, Folder 46)
    - Condoms, December 1985 (Carton 4, Folder 47)
    - Antibody Testing, 1985-1987 (Carton 4, Folder 48)
    - Research & Decisions Corporation: "Summary ... from Qualitative Research with Sexual Active Heterosexual Risk Group Audience", 1986 (Carton 4, Folder 49)
    - Center Magazine, 1984-1986 (Carton 4, Folder 50)
    - AZT Update, October 1986 (Carton 4, Folder 51)
    - AIDS Prevention - Gay and Bisexual Men in SF, June 1986 (Carton 4, Folder 52)
    - "Reaching Ethnic Communities in the Fight Against AIDS", August 1986 (Carton 4, Folder 53)
    - AIDS Information for Sexual Assault Survivors, May 1986 (Carton 4, Folder 54)
    - Nancy's Timelines, 1984-1987 (Carton 4, Folder 55)
    - Heterosexual Outreach, February 1986 (Carton 4, Folder 56)
    - Heterosexual Focus Groups, March/April 1986 (Carton 4, Folder 57)
    - Readability of Educational Materials, 1986 (Carton 4, Folder 58)
    - Materials sent to Pat Evans, Spring 1987 (Carton 4, Folder 59)
    - Heterosexual Focus Groups, Spring 1987 (Carton 4, Folder 60)
    - "Straight Talk" pamphlet, 1986-1987 (Carton 4, Folder 61)
    - Letter responding to Randy Shilts' article on "S.F. Hookers who made AIDS History", 1987 (Carton 4, Folder 62)
    - Women & AIDS Clinical Resource Guide, September 1987 (Carton 4, Folder 63)
    - Dental Manual, October 1987 (Carton 4, Folder 64)
    - "Your Child & AIDS" brochure Update, October 1987 (Carton 4, Folder 65)
    - Education Department - Planning, 1986-1987 (Carton 4, Folder 66)
      General
      (The oversized "Women & Children Plan" has been moved to the oversized Posters Folder)
    - Virginia Harris [Communications] Workshops, 1987 (Carton 4, Folder 67)
    - Women and AIDS - Support Network, 1986-1987 (Carton 4, Folder 68)
      Some items removed for confidentiality reasons - see folder 8/46 at end of collection
    - Miscellaneous items, 1985-1988; undated (Carton 4, Folder 69)
    - AIDS Educator Catalogues, 1986-1988 (Carton 4, Folder 70)
    - SFAF Annual Reports, 1985-1993 (Carton 4, Folder 71)
    - Impetus: SFAF Publication, 1987; 1989-1993 (Carton 5, Folder 1)
    - F.Y.I. AIDS (SFAF weekly AIDS Reader), 1988-1989 (Carton 5, Folder 2)
    - Advance Newsletter, 1990-1994 (Carton 5, Folder 3)
    - Intravenous Drug Users (IVDU) (Carton 5, Folder 4-29)
      - SFAF Drug Issues, 1985; 1987 (Carton 5, Folder 4)
      - SFAF Drug Rehabilitation Resources, 1985; 1988 (Carton 5, Folder 5)
      - AIDS and the IVDU - NIDA Training, September 10-12, 1986 (Carton 5, Folder 6)
      - "Neutral Zones: AIDS Epidemiology in the War on Drugs" by Jerry Mandel and Michael Aldrich, 1989 (Carton 5, Folder 7)
      - Papers by More Downing (Carton 5, Folder 8-9)
        - "'Cracking' The Community" [draft], February 1988 (Carton 5, Folder 8)
        - "Prevention Theory, AIDS & IV Drug Users" [draft], March 1988 (Carton 5, Folder 9)
      - Barbara Foster Associates - "AIDS in the Tenderloin: Needs Assessment", March 1988 (Carton 5, Folder 10)
      - Don CIRCA Des Jarlais - "Intravenous Drug Use and AIDS", April 1988 (Carton 5, Folder 11)
      - Samuel R. Freidman & Don CIRCA Des Jarlais - "Dimensions of Prevention Programs for Intravenous Drug Users and Their Sex Partners", June 1988 (Carton 5, Folder 12)
      - National AIDS Demonstration Research Project - "AIDS Initial Assessment Questionnaire: AIA-8.0", June 1988 (Carton 5, Folder 13)
      - Don CIRCA Des Jarlais & Samuel R. Friedman - "AIDS 88: HIV and Intravenous Drug Use", July 1988 (Carton 5, Folder 14)
      - Samuel R. Friedman - "Syringe Availability and AIDS", November 1988 (Carton 5, Folder 15)
      - Don CIRCA Des Jarlais & Samuel R. Friedman - "HIV Infection Among Persons Who Inject Illicit Drugs: Problems and Prospects" in Journal of Acquired Immune Deficiency Syndromes, 1988 (Carton 5, Folder 16)
      - Don CIRCA Des Jarlais et al. - "Chapter 6: AIDS and Needle Sharing Within the IV-Drug Use Subculture" in The Social Dimensions of AIDS, undated (Carton 5, Folder 17)
      - Samuel Friedman, et al. - "Risk Reduction Among Intravenous Drug Users In and Out of Treatment", 1988 (Carton 5, Folder 18)
      - Samuel R. Friedman - "AIDS, IV Drug Users, and American Dreams", May 1987 (Carton 5, Folder 19)
      - Don CIRCA Des Jarlais et al. - "AIDS and Preventing Initiation into Intravenous (IV) Drug Use", 1987 (Carton 5, Folder 20)
      - Samuel R. Friedman et al. - "The AIDS Epidemic among Blacks and Hispanics" in The Milbank Quarterly, 1987 (Carton 5, Folder 21)
      - Don CIRCA Des Jarlais et al. - "HIV-1 Infection Among Intravenous Drug Users in Manhattan, New York City, 1977-1987" (Carton 5, Folder 22)
      - Samuel R. Friedman et al. - (Carton 5, Folder 23-24)
        - "An Overview of AIDS Prevention Efforts Aimed at Intravenous Drug Users circa 1987" (Carton 5, Folder 23)
        - "AIDS and Self Organization among Intravenous Drug Users", 1987 (Carton 5, Folder 24)
      - Harold M. Ginzberg et al. - "Health Education and Knowledge Assessment of HTLV-III Diseases among Intravenous Drug Users", 1986 (Carton 5, Folder 25)
      - "The AIDS Arena and Drug Addiction", circa 1986 (Carton 5, Folder 26)